[{"answer": "The Slaughtered Lamb", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "That's a wolf's head", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Of course, The Slaughtered Lamb.  Why else would they have a severed fox head on a spear as their symbol", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Of course, The Slaughtered Lamb.  Why else would they have a severed wolf's head on a spear as their symbol", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "A coyote", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "The Hound of the that place", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "The Hound of the that place", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Shit!  my friend, what is that", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Come on, where", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Nice doggie.  Good boy", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Walking away, yes, sir.  Here we are walking away", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Where am I", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "that place?  Where's my friend?  I had a strange dream", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "my friend's dead", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Everything's in order?  What are you talking about", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Do you have bad dreams, too", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Yes, but does everyone kill my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Hello, my friend", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "No what", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "The American?  Yes, duck", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "What do you mean,", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " You're a very beautiful girl", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I was.  What are you reading", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Now what do you want to talk about", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " My best friend.  My very best friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "my friend, now I know this may be hard for you, but I have to warn you", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I'm a grisly sight, it's tru", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Your dead friend my friend", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What do I think?  You mean about the possibility of your becoming a monster in two days or about visits from dead friends", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I was dreaming again", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " Yeah, I would think so, too", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "He was talking about werewolves and monsters and as I was near here I thought...", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I thought I'd look into the boy's story", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Anything", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "It's silly of you to be apprehensive", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "How are we feeling tonight", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "No what", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "No", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "That's easy for you to say", "docId": "American-Werewolf-in-London.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " Why are you doing this to me", "qsentId": 44}]